[Music]
[Applause]
learn from the best brains in the world
and attend Master Class they leer to
develop sales leaders who are both
resilient as well as future proof at FWD
Indonesia we are committed to empowering
our passionate agent through a strong
and throughout training program that
build confidence leaders they not only
learn from Top inser Professor but also
connect with leading agent from across
FWD Market exchanging best practice and
insights the insight and perspective I
gain during the program reshape my
approach to problem solving and decision
making I got a sharpen my leadership
skill and learn how to handle challenges
in our effort changing
industry it's awesome to see how much
FWD invest in our growth and development
if you are ready to put in the effort
and strive for Success come along and
Embark this fulfilling Journey with
[Music]
FWD join us on this reward sping journey
and discover how you can take your
leadership skills and business
performance to the next level with our
world class program